Guide to the Robert Becker papers, ca. 1970-1990
Becker, Robert papers, ca. 1970-1990
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert Becker papers, ca. 1970-1990
21-25-2945
Robert Becker.
1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, articles, research notes, seed catalogs, and other material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, articles, and research notes concerning horticulture; also seed catalogs, and other material relating to fairs and all aspects of gardening.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Robert Becker was Professor of Horticulture at the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, articles, and research notes concerning horticulture; also seed catalogs, and other material relating to fairs and all aspects of gardening.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Becker, Robert F.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Faculty.; Cornell University--Faculty.
Subjects:
Horticulture--Study and teaching.; Gardening--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Tomato article for Cornell Plantations, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Shaker Seed Garden (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Hancock Shaker (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Shakers (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Early horticulturalists, writers, literature (Box 1, Folder 9)
- History of seed companies--Articles on seed catalogs (Box 1, Folder 10)
- History of seed companies--Articles on seed catalogs (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Calvin Keeney--Plant breeder (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Calvin Keeney--Plant breeder (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Carol Henry's articles on heirloom gardening and market gardening articles (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Marketing and transporting--Information (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Food processing articles (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Food processing articles (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Southern market and truck--Becker's notes (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Fine gardening article--Becker (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Hotbeds, cookery, vegetable industry in N.Y.S.--Article (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Fearing Burr research (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Fearing Burr research (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Fearing Burr article (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Elizabeth Daniel's article--mentions Becker (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Horticulture science article (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Article on beets (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Joseph Prentis--18th-century gardener (Box 1, Folder 27)
- A Treatise on Gardening--by a citizen of Virginia (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Book review--David Tucker's Kitchen Gardening in America (Box 1, Folder 29)
- County fairs (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Old Sturbridge Fall Fair (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Genesee County Fair (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Apples-Articles (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Berries (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Cider (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Fruit (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Grapes and wine (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Heather apples (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Hops and dyes (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Landscaping--Ornamental gardening (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Nurseries (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Root crops (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Root crops for livestock (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Genesee County Seed Project (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Carrier, Lyman, The Beginnings of Agriculture in America (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Becker's notes (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Becker's notes (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Becker's notes (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Articles by Becker (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Articles--Botany (Box 1, Folder 50)
- The Historical Gardener (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Seed catalogs--Old ones (Box 1, Folder 52)